name: 'There was / there were'
questions:
  -
    question: '$ an airport in 1967?'
    answers:
      - 'Were there'
      - 'There was'
      - 'Was there'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ milk in the fridge yesterday.'
    answers:
      - 'There is'
      - 'There was'
      - 'There were'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ Wi-Fi in your hotel room?'
    answers:
      - 'There was'
      - 'Were there'
      - 'Was there'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ a lot of people at my birthday party last week.'
    answers:
      - 'There were'
      - 'There was'
      - 'Was there'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ a swimming pool?'
    answers:
      - 'There was'
      - 'Were there'
      - 'Was there'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ any cafes near our house when we lived in England.'
    answers:
      - 'There was'
      - 'There wasn''t'
      - 'There weren''t'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ a bank?'
    answers:
      - 'There was'
      - 'Was there'
      - 'Were there'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ the Internet in our office last month.'
    answers:
      - 'There wasn''t'
      - 'There weren''t'
      - 'There isn''t'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ a bathtub in your bathroom?'
    answers:
      - 'There was'
      - 'There were'
      - 'Was there'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ any tourists in the museum yesterday.'
    answers:
      - 'There were'
      - 'There wasn''t'
      - 'There weren''t'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ any dictionaries in the classroom?'
    answers:
      - 'Were there'
      - 'Was there'
      - 'There were'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ a piano in the room.'
    answers:
      - 'There were'
      - 'There was'
      - 'There are'
    correct: 2
